The Guide to the American Short Line Railroad Association records, 1912-1971
American Short Line Railroad Association records, 1912-1971
- Series II. Procedural Files, 1912-1967.
  - Hours of Service Act S.2180; Oct. 3-4, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Hours of Service Act S.2180; June 28, 29, 191966 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Hearing transcripts
  - Hours of Service Act S.2180; 1966 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Statement
  - Hours of Servide Act S.2180; Oct. 3-4, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Hours of Service Act S.2180; Aug. 22/25, 191966 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Hours of Service Act S.2180; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Hours of Service Act S.2180; Sept. 1, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Hearing transcript
  - Hours of Service Act S.2180; Sept. 7, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Hours of Service Act H.R.13674; June 24, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Hours of Service Act H.R. 5196; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Hours of Service Act; June 24, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Hours of Service Act; 6-66 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Students
  - Hours of Service Act; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Hours of Service Act; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Hours of Service Act; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Hours of Service Act; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Hours of Service Act; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Hours of Service Act; June 27, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Hours of Service Act; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Hours of Service Act; Aug. 2, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Hours of Service Act; June 24, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Hours of Service Act; June 27, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Hours of Service Act; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Hours of Service Act; n.d. (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Hours of Service Act; [1966] (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Hours of Service Act; [1966] (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Hours of Service Act; [1966] (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Hours of Service Act; Aug. 1, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Hours of Service Act; Mar. 26, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Hours of Service Act; Aug. 29, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Hours of Service Act; Sept. 9, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Hours of Service Act; Sept. 12, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Hours of Service Act; Sept. 16, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Annual Report of Creditable Compensation; 1945-1964 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Statistical reports, correspondence
  - Bank Deposit Slips; May 6, 1966 to Dec. 31, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Duplicate deposit slips, adding machine tape
  - Bills sent for Dues; Jan. 66 to 3, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Bills
  - Blue Cross; 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Report forms, cards, pamphlets, newsletters, brochure
  - Group Hospitalization; July 20, 1953 to Nov. 1, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, instruction booklet, invoices
  - Miscellaneous Bookkeeping File; Aug. 6, 1962 to July 19, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Newsletters, reports, agenda, correspondence
  - Employer's Quarterly or Annual Report of Contributions; Sept. 30, 1939 to Dec. 31, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Forms, correspondence, reports
  - Employer's Quarterly Federal Tax Return; Mar. 31, 1943 to Sept. 30, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Returns, instructions, correspondence
  - Employer's Quarterly Railroad Retirement Tax Return; Sept. 30, 1937 to Jan. 14, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Tax forms, correspondence, instructions
  - Membership Cards; n.d. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    File cards
  - Miscellaneous Railroad Retirement Board Correspondence; Sept. 1, 1948 to Jan. 10, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Correspondence, forms, pamphlets
  - Miscellaneous Old Tax Books, Forms, Reports, Guides; 1957 to 1966 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Pamphlets
  - Miscellaneous Old Taxbooks, Forms, Reports, Guides; 1962, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Reconciliation of Income Tax Withheld from Wages; 1940-1964 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Tax forms, correspondence, work sheets
  - Supplemental Retirement Plan; 1954-1960 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Memos, reports
  - Treasury Bills, Section I; Jan. 12, 1959 to Nov. 26, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Statements, memos
- Series III. Active Member Files, 1913, 191966.
  Retired files, arranged alphabetically, of railroads which were active members of the Association, c. 1966. Records present a brief picture of the history of each line and include, not only routine membership correspondence with the Association, but also reports, applications, and exhibits of financial data for cases before the Interstate Commerce Commission, for which the Association often acted as statutory agent and legal counsel for its member lines. The files of some railroads include only the record of per diem questions. The files of many of the older members provide information concerning the railroads compensation claims against the United States under the provision of the Transportation Act of 1920.
  - Ahnapee and Western Railway Green Bay, wisc; June 1, 1947 to Nov. 24, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 1-14)
    Correspondence, legislative bills, lists, memos, drawings, booklets, reports, photos, petitions
    Correspondents: Verne M. Bushman; Interstate Commerce Commission
  - Aberdeen and Rockfish Railroad Aberdeen, North [UNK]; June 6, 1917 to May 3, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
    Correspondence, questionnaires, figures, lists of, ICC orders, sale agreement
  - Akron, Canton and Youngstown Railroad, akron, Ohio; Nov. 18, 1955 to Jan. 16, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Pamphlet, statement, correspondence
  - Albany and Northern Railway Co. Cordele, Coa. to albamy, Coa; 1951, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, report (based in Moultrie, Ga)
  - Alexander Railroad, [UNK], North Carolina; Jan. 2, 1946 to Sept. 15, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
    Correspondence, figures, lists of
  - Algers, Winslow and Western Railway Co. Cleveland, Ohio; Dec. 31, 1931 to Jan. 13, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
  - Aliquippa and Southern Railroad Pittsburgh, Pa; 1957 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Magazine
  - Angelina and Neches River Railroad Keltys, Texas; Mar. 27, 1923 to Apr. 19, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 11-13)
  - Apache Railway Co. McNARY, Arizina; Feb. 23, 1921 to Nov. 26, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 14-15)
    Correspondence, magazine
  - Apalachicola Northern Railroad Port St. Joe, Florida; Oct. 3, 1913 to Apr. 1, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 16-18)
    Correspondence, ICC orders, news article, booklet
  - Arcade and Attica Railroad Grcade, New York; Jan. 28, 1918 to Apr. 11, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 19-22)
    Correspondence, ICC orders, financial statements
  - Arcata and Mad River Railroad Korblex, Calif. to Korbel, Calif; Apr. 24, 1926 to Nov. 20, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 23-24)
  - Arkansas and Louisiana Missouri Railway Co. Shreve [UNK], Louisiana; Apr. 12, 1917 to Mar. 15, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 25-28)
    Correspondence, ICC reports
  - Ashley, Drew and Northern Railway Crossett, Arkansas; Nov. 5, 1920 to Feb. 11, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 1-4)
    Correspondence, circular, memos, settlement, reports, pams, stationery
  - Atlanta and St. Andrews Bay Railway Dothan, Alabama; Jan. 3, 1919 to Nov. 3, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 5-11)
    Correspondence, ICC orders, stock certificates, newsletter, legal brief, reports, statistics, memos
  - Atlantic and East Carolina Railway New Bern, North Carolina; Aug. 19, 1935 to Nov. 30, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 12-18)
    Correspondence, ICC orders, company notes, leases, freight tariffs, newsletter, article, reports, statistics
    Ownership of railway, tariffs, per diem, railway operation
  - Atlantic and Western Railway Sanford, North Carolina; May 10, 1917 to July 3, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 19-20)
  - Baltimore and Annapolis Railroad Baltimore, Maryland; Feb. 15, 1949 to June 29, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Beech Mountain Railroad Co. Clarksburg, West Virginia; June 14, 1954 to Mar. 13, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
  - Belfast and Moosehead Lake Railroad Belfast, Maine; Sept. 7, 1920 to Nov. 21, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
    Correspondence, report, charts
  - Bellefonte Central Railroad Bellefonte, Pennsylvania; Oct. 15, 1926 to Dec. 31, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
    Report, correspondence, charts, statistics
  - Belton Railroad Smith, Texas to Belton, Texas; Feb. 1, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Bevier and Southern Railroad Bevier, Maine; Nov. 5, 1920 to Jan. 16, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 9-10)
    Correspondence, exhibits
  - Birmingham Southern Railroad Fair Field, Alabama; Mar. 14, 1921 to Dec. 31, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 11-12)
    Correspondence, rates, brief, bound volumes
  - Bonhomie and Hattiesburg Southern Railroad Fernwood, Mississippi; Nov. 24, 1936 to Sept. 14, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Boston and Maine Railroad Boston, Massachusetts; Feb. 26, 1951 to May 19, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 14-18)
    Reports, correspondence, news articles, statement, statistical charts
  - Brooklyn Eastern District Terminal Brooklyn, New York; Nov. 24, 1959 to Mar. 23, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    Report, brochure
  - Bush Terminal Railroad Brooklyn, New York; Mar. 3, 1921 to Feb. 20, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 20-23)
    Correspondence, reports, map, blueprints
  - Butte, Anaconda and Pacific Railway Anaconda, Montana; Mar. 1, 1918 to Nov. 21, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 24-27)
    Correspondence, drawings, ICC application, report, blueprints, statistical data
  - Cadiz Railroad Company Cadiz, Kentucky; Aug. 10, 1920 to Dec. 10, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
    Correspondence, applications, testimony exhibits
  - California Western Railroad San Francisco, California; Oct. 30, 1920 to Mar. 21, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 3-7)
    Correspondence, statistical data, memo, booklet, blueprints
  - Camino, Placerville and Lake Tahoe Railroad Camino, California; Nov. 5, 1920 to Aug. 5, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
  - Canton Railroad Company Baltimore, Maryland; Dec. 10, 1918 to Mar. 14-27, 1941, 1961, 191963 (Box 19, Folder 10-11)
    Correspondence, booklets
  - Canton and Carthage Railroad Canton, Mississippi; Mar. 24, 1932 to Sept. 7, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 12-13)
    Correspondence, statistical data, booklet
  - Cape Fear Railway Inc. Fort Bragg, North Carolina; Jan. 18, 1932 to Apr. 8, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Carbon County Railway San Francisco, California; Mar. 25, 1925 to Mar. 18, 1936, [1961] (Box 19, Folder 15-16)
    Correspondence, booklet
  - Carolina Western Railroad Franklin, Virginia; Nov. 24, 1920 to Oct. 29, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 17-19)
    Correspondence, statistical data, reports, blueprints
  - Cedar Rapids and Iowa City Railway Cedar Rapids, Iowa; Dec. 6, 1920 to Aug. 21, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 20-21)
  - Chattahoochee Valley Railway West Point, Georgia; Apr. 7, 1919 to Aug. 4, 1950, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 22-25)
    Correspondence, booklet, maps
  - Chesapeake Western Railway Harrisonburg, Virginia; May 1, 1917 to June 4, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 26-31)
    Letterhead reads: Chesapeake Western Railroad
    Correspondence, map, application, charter, By-laws, booklet, ICC orders, memo
  - Chicago Shortline Railway Chicago, Illinois; Nov. 5, 1920 to Mar. 30, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Chicago, South Shore and South Bend Railroad Michigan City, Indiana; May 1919 to May 1956 (Box 20, Folder 2-12)
    Correspondence, legislative bill, state meets, contracts, reports, statistical data, drawings, lists, maps
    Postal service, per diem, urban transportation, railroad reorganization
    Correspondents: Dwight Palmer, Comm., N.J. Highway Dept. W. P. Coliton, Pres: R.R.
  - City of Prineville Railway Prineville, Oregon; Nov. 14, 1949 to Sept. 25, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 13-15)
    Correspondence, forms, booklet
  - Claremont and Concord Railway Co. Boston, Massachusetts; Jan. 5, 1955 to Jan. 12, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Clarendon and Pittsford Railroad Proctor, Vermont; Dec. 23, 1920 to Sept. 22, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 1-3)
    Correspondence, statistical data, maps, work sheets
  - Cliffside Railroad Co. Cliffside, North Carolina; Sept. 18, 1917 to May 26, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 4-5)
    Correspondence, statistical data, forms
  - Colorado and Wyoming Railway Denver, Colorado; Dec. 1, 1948 to Jan. 2, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, forms
  - Columbia and Cowlitz Railway Co. Longview, Washington; Sept. 19, 1927 to Dec. 26, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 7-8)
  - Corinth and Counce Railroad Co. Counce, Tennessee; June 22, 1959 to Oct. 29, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 9-10)
  - Rutland Construction
  - Coudersport and Port Allegany Railroad Coudersport, Pennsylvania; Apr. 8, 1919 to June 24, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 11-13)
    Reports, correspondence, figures
  - Cuyahoga Valley Railway Cleveland, Ohio; Oct. 1, 1944 to Oct. 10, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Dansville and Mount Morris Railroad Dansville, New York; Dec. 3, 1920 to Dec. 14, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 15-17)
    Correspondence, reports, statistical data
  - Dardanelle and Russellville Railroad McAlester, Oklahoma president); Nov. 5, 1920 to Dec. 22, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 18-19)
    Designation of statutory agent (general manager) Janet - which address do I use?
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Albany, New York; Dec. 15, 1942 to Apr. 11, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 20-22)
    Correspondence, booklet, report
  - Delray Connecting Railroad Detroit, Michigan; Jan. 25, 1921 to Feb. 17, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 21-23)
  - Delta Valley and Southern Railway Wilson, Arkansas; Sept. 5, 1934 to Dec. 4, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 24-25)
  - Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Denver, Colorado; Sept. 20, 1920 to Nov. 8-57, 1962, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 26-31)
    Reports, correspondence, booklets
    Abandonment, railroad problems, annual reports, designation of statutory agent, history of transportation, Colorado
  - DeQueen and Eastern Railroad DeQueen, Arkansas; Dec. 28, 1917 to June 22, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
    Correspondence, reports, financial statistics
  - Des Moines and Central Iowa Railway Des Moines, Iowa; Feb. 26, 1918 to Nov. 13, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 3-8)
    Correspondence, forms, brochure, reports, legislative bills
  - Detroit and Mackinac Railway Tawas City, Michigan; Sept. 1, 1920 to July 20, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 9-15)
    Correspondence, legislative bills, reports, maps, booklets
  - Duluth and Northeastern Railroad Cloquet, Minnesota, moved to St. Paul, Minnesota; Nov. 5, 1920 to Aug. 11, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 16-17)
    Correspondence, broadside, advertisement
  - Duluth Missabe and Iron Range Railway Duloth, Minnesota; 1958-1964 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    Magazines, article, picture
  - East Erie Commercial Railroad Erie, Pennsylvania; Jan. 12, 1921 to July 1, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 19-21)
  - East Jersey Railroad and Terminal Co. New York City, New York; moved to Bayonne, new Jersey; Aug. 14, 1918 to Mar. 26, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 22-23)
    Correspondence, trust notes
  - East Tennessee and Western North Carolina Railroad Johnson City, Tennessee; May 30, 1923 to Oct. 2, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - East Washington Railway Seat Pleasant, Maryland; Nov. 5, 1920 to Sept. 6, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Escanaba and Lake Superior Railroad Wells, Michigan; Nov. 5, 1920 to July 12, 1941, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 26-28)
    Correspondence, tariffs, statistical data, photo
  - Fairport, Painesville and Eastern Railroad Painseville, Ohio; Nov. 5, 1920 to Feb. 23, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Feather River Railway Land, California; Dec. 23, 1944 to Feb. 14, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Fernwood, Columbia and Gulf Railroad Fernwood, Mississipp; Oct. 30, 1920 to June 4, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 3-5)
    Correspondence, statistical data, reprints
  - Fonda, Johnstown and Gloversville Railway Gloversville, New York; June 18, 1919 to June 27, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 6-9)
    Correspondence, reports, ICC orders, sketch, exhibits
  - Fordyce and Princeton Railroad, Fordyce, Arkansas; Sept. 27, 1920 to Aug. 10, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    ICC orders, correspondence
  - Fore River Railroad Quincy, Massachusetts; Mar. 7, 1927 to Feb. 24, 1932 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Fort Dodge, Des Moines and Southern Railway Boone, Iowa; June 5, 1953 to Dec. 14, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 12-14)
    ICC reports, applications, exhibits, correspondence
  - Frankfort and Cincinnati Railroad Lexington, Kentucky; moved to Frankfort, Kentucky; Mar. 3, 1921 to Apr. 28, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 15-16)
    Correspondence, statistical data, map
  - Gainesville Midland Railroad Co. Gainesville, Georgia; May 4, 1917 to May 17, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 17-18)
    Correspondence, reports, map
  - Genesee and Wyoming Railroad Retsof, New York; Nov. 5, 1920 to May 22, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 19-20)
    Correspondence, statistical data, map, charts, booklets
  - Georgetown Railroad Georgetown, Texas; Jan. 29, 1929 to Dec. 31, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Georgia and Florida Railroad Augusta, Georgia; Mar. 3, 1921 to Mar. 6, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 2-5)
    Correspondence, reports, schedules
  - Georgia, Ashburn, Sylvester and Camilla Railway Moultrie, Georgia; Feb. 21, 1924 to June 1, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 6-7)
  - Georgia Northern Railway Moultrie, Georgia; Sept. 21, 1920 to Aug. 15, 1958, 1963, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 8-11)
    Correspondence, proceedings, application, memos, article
  - Grafton and Upton Railroad Hopedale, Mass; Nov. 5, 1920 to Oct. 22, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Graham County Railroad Robbinsville, North Carolina; Jan. 26, 1932 to Jan. 28, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, reports, exhibits
  - Graysonia, Nashville and Ashdown Railroad Denver, Colorado; Aug. 17, 1954 to Sept. 7, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Great Southwest Railroad Fort Worth-Dallas, Texas area?; Nov. 1, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 15-16)
  - Green Mountain Railroad Bellows Falls, Vermont; 1-65 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    Contract
  - Greenville and Northern Railway Greenville, North Carolina; Dec. 17, 1920 to Apr. 22, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 18-22)
    Correspondence, booklets, reports
  - Hampton and Branchville Railroad Hampton, South Carolina; Dec. 28, 1917 to Feb. 26, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 23-26)
    Application, correspondence, exhibits
  - High Point, Thomasville and Denton Railroad High Point, North Carolina; May 22, 1917 to May 8, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 1-7)
    Correspondence, booklets, brochures, reports, briefs, statistical data
    Construction, acquisition of line, switching charges, house organ, per diem
  - Hoosac Tunnel and Wilmington Railroad Wilmington, Vermont; Mar. 4, 1927 to Jan. 10, 1938 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Hutchinson and Northern Hutchinson, Kansas; May 12, 1926 to Mar. 16, 1936 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Iowa Terminal Railroad Mason City, Iowa; Aug. 16, 1918 to Feb. 15, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 10-13)
    Applications, statistical data, blueprint correspondence
  - Jerseyville and Eastern Railroad Jerseyville, Illinois; Sept. 1, 1950 to May 14, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 14-15)
  - Johnstown and Stony Creek Railroad Johnstown, Pennsylvania; Nov. 5, 1920 to Feb. 16, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 16-17)
    ICC order, correspondence
  - Kansas City Public Service Freight Operation Kansas City, Missouri; 1963, 11-23-65 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    Report, map
  - Kentucky and Tennessee Railway Stearns, Kentucky; Dec. 7, 1918 to Oct. 15, 19[58] (Box 25, Folder 19-21)
    Correspondence, exhibit, booklet
  - Lake Erie, Franklin and Clarion Railroad Clarion, Pennsylvania; Nov. 5, 1920 to Oct. 10, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 22-23)
    Correspondence, exhibits, blueprints
  - Lake Terminal Railroad Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania; Jan. 5, 1921 to Mar. 14, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Lancaster and Chester Railway Lancaster, South Carolina; Apr. 28, 1920 to Aug. 6, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 25-26)
  - Laona and Northern Railway Laona, Wisconsin; Nov. 5, 1920 to Aug. 5, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 27-28)
    Correspondence, forms, reports
  - LaSalle and Bureau County Railroad LaSalle, Illinois; Nov. 5, 1920 to Apr. 29, 1926 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Laurinburg and Southern Railroad Laurinburg, North Carolina; Jan. 3, 1921 to Dec. 2, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    Correspondence, forms, exhibits, statistical data
  - Lehigh and Hudson River Railway Warwick, New York; Dec. 31, 1961 to Dec. 31, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Live Oak, Perry and Gulf Railroad Live Oak, Florida; Oct. 3, 1913 to Mar. 10, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 2-4)
    Correspondence, reports, agreement, map
  - Longview, Portland and Northern Railway Longview, Washington; Dec. 22 to July 27, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 5-7)
    Reports, correspondence, bound volume, drawing, petitions
  - Louisiana and Northwest Railroad Homer, Louisiana; Mar. 6, 1959 to Apr. 1, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Manufacturer's Junction Railway Cicero, Illinois; Jan. 7, 1922 to Nov. 13, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 9-10)
  - Marianna and Blountstown Railroad Blountstwn, Florida; Oct. 30, 1920 to Apr. 8, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 11-12)
    Correspondence, statistical exhibits
  - Marinette, Tomahawk and Western Railroad Tomahawk, Wisconsin; Aug. 23, 1923 to Feb. 5, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 13-14)
  - Maryland and Pennsylvania Railroad Baltimore, Maryland; Dec. 14, 1920 to 1963 (Box 26, Folder 15-18)
    Report, correspondence, application, ICC orders
  - McCloud River Railroad McCloud, California; Apr. 28, 1917 to Sept. 13, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 19-22)
    Correspondence, certificate, application, exhibits
  - McKeesport Connecting Railroad Pittsburg, Pennsylvania; Apr. 2, 1926 to Mar. 10, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 23-24)
    Brochure, speech, booklet, correspondence
  - Meridian and Bigbee Railroad Meridian, Mississippi; July 25, 1941 to July 24, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 25-26)
    Correspondence, note, booklet
  - Middletown and New Jersey Railway Middletown, New York; Feb. 28, 1919 to Jan. 24, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
    Correspondence, exhibits, reports
  - Minneapolis, Northfield and Southern Railway Minneapolis, Minnesota; Jan. 24, 1921 to Mar. 31, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
    Applications, exhibits, correspondence
  - Mississippi and Skuna Valley Railroad Memphis, Tennessee; Jan. 29, 1931 to Feb. 11, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 5-6)
  - Mississippi Export Railroad Moss Point, Mississippi; July 30, 1929 to Apr. 22, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 7-10)
    Applications, resolution, correspondence
  - Mobile and Gulf Railroad Luisville, Kentucky; Sept. 5, 1927 to Mar. 15, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 11-12)
  - Monon Railroad Chicago, Illinois; Dec. 13, 1920 to 13-23, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 13-15)
    ICC order, booklet, correspondence
  - Montpelier and Barre Railroad Boston, Massachusetts; Jan. 21, 1951 to Nov. 14, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 16-18)
    Application, correspondence, reports
  - Morehead and North Fork Railroad Morehead, Kentucky; Aug. 28, 1920 to Oct. 4, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 19-22)
    Application, reports, lists, notes, correspondence
  - Morristown and Erie Railroad Whippany, New Jersey; Mar. 3, 1921 to Nov. 14, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Moscow, Camden and San Augustine Railroad Camden, Texas; Mar. 3, 1921 to Apr. 29, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 2-3)
  - Moshassuck Valley Railroad Saylesville, Rhode Island; Nov. 5, 1920 to May 12, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
    Application, correspondence
  - Mount Hood Railroad Baker, Oregon; Dec. 27, 1920 to May 27, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 6-7)
    Correspondence, exhibits, blueprint
  - Muncie and Western Railroad Muncie, Indiana; Feb. 20, 1924 to Oct. 25, 1932 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Narragansett Pier Railroad Wakefield, Rhode Island; Dec. 17, 1920 to Apr. 8, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 9-10)
  - New Jersey and New York Railroad New York City, New York; May 49 to Apr. 30, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 11-17)
    Reports, correspondence, booklets, petition, exhibits
  - New Orleans Public Belt Railroad New Orleans, Louisiana; Aug. 23, 1920 to Apr. 22, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 1-6)
    Correspondence, booklets, tariffs, brochure, legislative bill
  - New York Dock Railway New York City, New York; Mar. 3, 1921 to Feb. 20, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - New York, office in Paterson New Jersey & New York City, New York Susquehanna and Western Railway; Aug. 18, 1939 to Dec. 23, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 8-14)
    Reports, correspondence
  - Norfolk, Franklin and Danville Norfolk, Virginia; July 28, 1948 to June 27, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 1-4)
    Reports, correspondence, exhibits, booklet